Guide to the J. E. Wallace Sterling, President of Stanford University, Papers
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Papers, Series 1
  - Scholarships - David L. Sloan and Lavinia E. Sloan Memorial: Chemistry, 1945-1951 (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - Scholarships - William H. Sloan and Myrtle B. Sloan, 1950-1951 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Alumni Association, 1936-1952 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of Chigao, 1941-1953 (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of Colorado, 1953 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of the Monterey Peninsula, 1949-1954 (Box 55, Folder 47)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of the North Bay, 1952-1953 (Box 55, Folder 48)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of Pomona Valley, Calif., 1949-1951 (Box 55, Folder 49)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of San Diego, 1948-1950 (Box 55, Folder 50)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of Saudi Arabia, 1950-1950 (Box 55, Folder 51)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of Seattle, 1947-1953 (Box 55, Folder 52)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of Taft, 1952 (Box 55, Folder 53)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Club of Washington DC, 1954 (Box 55, Folder 54)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Law Veterans Memorial, 1945-1950 (Box 55, Folder 55)
  - Scholarships - Stanford Student Nurses Loan Fund, 1939-1951 (Box 55, Folder 56)
  - Scholarships - Bruce Macon Tarver Mermorial, 1941-1954 (Box 55, Folder 57)
  - Fellowships - The Viking Fund: Anthropology, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 58)
    Changed to Wenner-Gren Foundation
  - Scholarships - Winnie Washburn, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 59)
  - Scholarships - Ephraim and Amelia Weiss, 1955 (Box 55, Folder 60)
  - Scholarships - Western die Casting company, 1951-1956 (Box 55, Folder 61)
  - Scholarships - Palmer Wilkinson Taylor, 1938-1952 (Box 55, Folder 62)
  - Scholarships - Charles W. Willard: Nursing, 1925-1952 (Box 55, Folder 63)
  - Scholarships - Dean Witter Scholarship Fund in Business, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 64)
  - Scholarships - Helen Perkins Witter, 1951 (Box 55, Folder 65)
  - Scholarships - Women's Architectural League, 1952-1953 (Box 55, Folder 66)
  - Scholarships - XYZ, 1935-1952 (Box 55, Folder 67)
  - Ford Fund for the Advancement of Education: General and Committee on Utilization of College Teaching Resources, 1955-1961 (Box 55, Folder 68)
  - Ford Fund for the Advancement of Education: W.H. Cowley, Production of a manuscript on higher education, 1961 (Box 55, Folder 69)
  - Funds - M.J. Allen Band Fund, 1950-1959 (Box 55, Folder 70)
  - Funds - Alumni Association Building Fund, 1949-1952 (Box 55, Folder 71)
  - Funds - Anonymous (Vander Poel), 1934-1952 (Box 55, Folder 72)
  - Funds - Alpha Phi Fund for Pediatrics, Cardiology, 1951-1955 (Box 55, Folder 73)
  - Funds - Helen Lucile Bailey Memorial, 1950 (Box 55, Folder 74)
  - Funds - Francis William Bergstrom, 1946-1951 (Box 55, Folder 75)
  - Funds - Eleanor Boyd Memorial, 1946-1951 (Box 55, Folder 76)
  - Funds - Mitsie Stauffer Briggs: Medical Fund, 1957 (Box 55, Folder 77)
  - Funds - Buck-of-the-Month Club (Buck Club), 1934-1952 (Box 55, Folder 78)
  - Funds - Mary S. Bullock, 1948-1949 (Box 55, Folder 79)
  - Funds - Crary Surgical Cardiovascular Research Laboratory, Allen and Gordon Crary Funds, 1957-1959 (Box 55, Folder 80)
  - Funds - Dean George B. Culver Memorial Fund, 1949-1951 (Box 55, Folder 81)
  - Funds - Dr. Clinton Cushing Free Bed Trust Fund, 1940-1951 (Box 55, Folder 82)
  - Funds - Paul M. and Francis S. Downing Fund, 1948-1950 (Box 55, Folder 83)
  - Funds - Charles A. Dukes Loan Fund for Medical Students, 1945-1951 (Box 55, Folder 84)
  - Funds - Endowment Accounts Authorizations "A - R", 1911-1954 (Box 55, Folder 85)
  - Funds - Endowment Account Authorizations "S - Z", 1927-1955 (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Funds - Engineering Loan Fund, 1945-1950 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Funds - Shelagh Galligan Free Bed Endowment Fund, 1948-1951 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Funds - Domingo Ghirardelli Memorial Book Fund, 1940-1950 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Funds - Gilfillan Building Fund, 1955-1957 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Funds - Philip K. Gilman Memorial Revolving Fund, 1948-1951 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Funds - Hoover Library Film Project Fund, 1955-1958 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Funds - Kaufman Leukemia Fund, 1948-1951 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Funds - P, 1939-1952 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Funds - Harris J. and Katherine Ryan Fund, 1939-1950 (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Funds - Dr. Scarborough's Post Graduate Fund, 1939-1950 (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Funds - Stanford Business School Fund, 1953-1954 (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Funds - Stanford University Fund, 1934-1955 (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Funds - John M. Switzer Student Loan Fund, 1937-1951 (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Budget, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Misc. (Clippings), 1949 (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Inaugural Invitations (to inaugurations elsewhere), 1949-1950 (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Budget, 1959 (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Invitations, Distinguished Participants, Summary, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - Sterling Inauguration - General Arrangements, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Report, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Educational Institutions Invited, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Misc., 1949 (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Misc., 1949 (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Press Releases, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Invitations: Foundations and Learned Societies, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 26)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Publicity Clippings, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 27)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Misc. correspondence, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 28)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Schools Declining Invitations, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 29)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Schools Accepting Invitations A - K, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 30)
  - Sterling Inauguration - Schools Accepting Invitations L - Z, 1949 (Box 56, Folder 31)
  - Planning, Director of - Organization of Planning Dept., E.T. Spencer, 1944-1956 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Planning, Director of - Report to the President, 1948-1949 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Planning, Director of, 1950-1951 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Planning, Director of, 1951-1952 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Planning, Director of, 1952-1953 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Planning, Director of, 1953-1954 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Buildings, 1949-1950 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Planning - Comments on Architecture and Planning, etc., 1949-1955 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Planning - Memorial Auditorium Alterations, Lighting, etc., 1953-1959 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Planning Office Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Planning - General, 1954-1955 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Planning - General, 1955-1956 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Planning - General, 1956-1958 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Planning - General, 1959-1964 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Planning - Fraternity House Surveys, 1955-1957 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Planning - John Carl Warnecke, Architect, 1955-1958 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Planning - El Camino Real Improvements, 1955-1959 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Planning - Junipero Serra Freeway, 1956-1959 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Planning - Sports Pavilion (Basketball Pavilion), 1956-1962 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Structural Reports on Individual Fraternity Houses, 1957 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Planning - Foothill Expressway, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Planning - Wagner and Martinez, Contracters, 1958 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Planning -Spencer and Lee, Architects (formerly Spencer and Ambrose), 1958-1959 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Planning - Supervising Architect, 1959 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Committees - General, 1943-1953 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Committees - Academic Council Executive Committee, 1954-1960 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Committees - Admissions and Advanced Standing, 1945-1960 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Committees - Athletics, 1951 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Committees - Dental Education, 1956-1957 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Committees - East Asian Studies, 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Committees - Executive Committee, 1945-1954 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Committees - Far Eastern Library, 1950 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Committees - Foreign Students, 1944-1953 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Committees - Committee for a Free Asia, 1950-1951 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Committees - Committee for a Free Asia, 1951-1952 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Committees - Committee for a Free Asia, 1952-1953 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Committees - Committee for a Free Asia, 1953-1954 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Graduate Study, 1944-1953 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Committee on Graduation, 1945-1952 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Committees - Honor Code, 1950-1953 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Committees - International Affairs, Research and Teaching, 1952-1953 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Committees - International Studies: East Asian Research, 1956-1957 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Committees - International Studies: East Asian Research, 1957-1959 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Committees - International Studies: East European Area, 1956-1967 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Committees - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, 1950-1953 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Committees - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, 1953-1954 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Committees - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, 1954-1955 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Committees - Advisory Committee on Land and Building Development, 1955-1956 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Committees - Library, 1947-1951 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Los Angeles County Transportation Problems Advisory Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Committees - Lower Division Committee, 1943-1952 (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Committees - Medical School, 1952-1953 (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Committees - Medical School: Clinical Committee, 1950-1953 (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Committees - Medical School: Clinical Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Committees - Medical School: Curriculum Committee, 1955 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Committees - Medical School: Committee on Research, 1945-1951 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Committees - Medical School, University Committee on, 1955-1956 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Committees - Nuclear Technology, 1956-1957 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Committees - Pacific Coast Committee for the Humanities, 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Committees - Pacific Coast Committee for the Humanities, 1952-1953 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Committees - Palo Alto Hospital Committee, 1946-1953 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Committees - Palo Alto/Stanford Committee, 1950-1951 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Committees - Patents, 1943-1953 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Committees - Standard Petroleum Investment Fund Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Committees - Premedical Students, 1945-1952 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Committees - Committee on the Present Danger, 1951-1952 (Box 59, Folder 12)
    Letters from Samuel Goldwyn inviting Sterling to join. He declined.
  - Committees - Public Exercises, 1948-1953 (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Public Exercises, 1953-1956 (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Public Health, 1947-1952 (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Committees - Radiation Hygiene, 1953-1957 (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Committees - Radio and TV, 1944-1952 (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Committees - Radio and TV, 1950-1952 (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Committees - Registration, 1945-1953 (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Committees - Research in Values in Contemporary Culture, 1951 (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Committees - Rhodes Scholarships, 1949-1953 (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Committees - Scholarship Commitee, 1945-1953 (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Committees - Stanford Business School Fund Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Committees - Stanford Corporate Gift Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Committees - Stanford Corporate Gift Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Committees - Stanford Corporate Gift Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Committees - Stanford University Fund, Annual Report, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Committees - Stanford Engineering Fund, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Committees - Stanford Engineering Fund, 1954-1955 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Committees - Stanford Fund Committee, 1952-1953 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Committees - Stanford Fund Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Committees - Stanford Fund Cornn ittee, 1955-1956 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Committees - Stanford '55 Heritage Fund Committee, 1955 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Committees - Stanford Medical Alumni Fund, 1954-1955 (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Committees - Stanford Parents Committee, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Committees - Stanford Parents Committee, 1955-1956 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Committees - Stanford Petroleum Investment Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Committees - Student Affairs, 1945-1954 (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Committees - Commission for Student Aid, 1949-1953 (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Committees - Student Enrollment, 1944-1951 (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Committees - Student/Faculty EmploymentCommittee, 1948-1951 (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Committees - Student/Faculty Educational Commission, 1950-1954 (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Committees - Student/Faculty Political Committee, 1951-1952 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Committees - Student/Faculty Relations Committee, 1954-1955 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - Committees - Student/Faculty Scholarship Committee, 1952 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  - Committees - Summer Quarter Development, 1947-1953 (Box 60, Folder 23)
  - Committees - Student Activities, 1951 (Box 60, Folder 24)
  - Committees - Supplementary Research Grants Committee, 1944-1953 (Box 60, Folder 25)
  - Committees - Teacher Education, 1953-1954 (Box 60, Folder 26)
  - Committees - Undergraduate Education, General Studies Committee, 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 27)
  - Committees - University Publications, 1947-1950 (Box 60, Folder 28)
  - Committees - Who's Who in Latin America Committee, 1943-1955 (Box 60, Folder 29)
  - Gifts - A, 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder 30)
  - Gifts - B, 1961-1962 (Box 60, Folder 31)
  - Gifts - Ba-BI, 1962-1965 (Box 60, Folder 32)
  - Gifts - Bm-Bz, 1962-1965 (Box 60, Folder 33)
  - Gifts - Bechtel Corporation, 1961-1965 (Box 60, Folder 34)
  - Gifts - Bethlehem Steel Co., 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 35)
  - Gifts - In Memory of James Black (Trustee), 1965 (Box 60, Folder 36)
  - Gifts - C, 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 37)
  - Gifts - Ca-Cl, 1963-1965 (Box 60, Folder 38)
  - Gifts - Cm-Cz, 1963-1965 (Box 60, Folder 39)
  - Gifts - Chase Manhattan Bank Foundation, 1958-1964 (Box 60, Folder 40)
  - Gifts - Class Endowment Funds '99 to 7, 1936-1963 (Box 60, Folder 41)
  - Gifts - D, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 42)
  - Gifts - D, 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder 43)
  - Gifts - E, 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder 44)
  - Gifts - F, 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 45)
  - Gifts - F, 1963-1964 (Box 60, Folder 46)
  - Gifts - Ford Motor Co. Matching Gifts, 1960-1961 (Box 60, Folder 47)
  - Gifts - G, 1960-1964 (Box 60, Folder 48)
  - Gifts - General Electric Foundation Matching Gifts, 1960-1965 (Box 60, Folder 49)
  - Gifts - Goodyear Foundation, Inc., 1960-1962 (Box 60, Folder 50)
  - Gifts - Gulf Oil Corp., 1961-1965 (Box 60, Folder 51)
  - Gifts - H, 1963-1964 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Gifts - Hercules Powder Co. Matching Gifts, 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Gifts - Hewlett-Packard Matching Gifts, 1956-1961 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Gifts - Honolulu Oil Corp., 1961 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Gifts - 1, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Gifts - International Business Machines (IBM), 1960-1964 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Gifts - J, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Gifts - K, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Gifts - Kaiser Steel Corp., 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Gifts - L, 1960-1962 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Gifts - L, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Gifts - M (minus Mac, Me), 1962-1963 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Gifts - Mac, Me, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 13)
  - Gifts - Matson Navigation Company, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 14)
  - Gifts - N, 1963-1964 (Box 61, Folder 15)
  - Gifts - Northrop Corp., 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 16)
  - Gifts - 0, 1963-1964 (Box 61, Folder 17)
  - Gifts - P, 1963-1964 (Box 61, Folder 18)
  - Gifts - Pacific Telephone Co., 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 19)
  - Gifts - Pacific Finance Corp., 1961-1962 (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Gifts - R, 1963-1964 (Box 61, Folder 21)
  - Gifts - Research Institute Gifts, 1947-1949 (Box 61, Folder 22)
  - Gifts - Richfield Oil Corp., 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 23)
  - Gifts - Sa-Sl, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Gifts - Sm-Sz, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 25)
  - Gifts - Socony Mobil Oil Co., 1960-1962 (Box 61, Folder 26)
  - Gifts - Standard Oil of California, 1956-1961 (Box 61, Folder 27)
  - Gifts - Stanford Research Institute (SRI), 1960-1961 (Box 61, Folder 28)
  - Gifts - T, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 29)
  - Gifts - Undergraduate Men's Housing, 1958-1962 (Box 61, Folder 30)
  - Gifts - Union Oil Co., 1961-1965 (Box 61, Folder 31)
  - Gifts - Utah Construction Co., 1961 (Box 61, Folder 32)
  - Gifts - W, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 33)
  - Gifts - XYZ, 1963 (Box 61, Folder 34)
  - Medical School and Hospital Historical File, 1945-1950 (Box 61, Folder 35)
  - Medical School, 1948-1949 (Box 61, Folder 36)
  - Medical School, 1949-1950 (Box 61, Folder 37)
  - Medical School, 1950-1951 (Box 61, Folder 38)
  - Medical School, 1951-1952 (Box 61, Folder 39)
  - Medical School, 1951-1953 (Box 61, Folder 40)
  - Medical School, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 41)
  - Medical School, 1952 (Box 61, Folder 42)
  - Medical School, 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 43)
  - Medical School, 1952-1953 (Box 61, Folder 44)
  - Medical School - Sept. to Jan., 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Medical School - Jan. to Aug., 1954 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Medical School - Sept. to Dec., 1954 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Medical School, 1955 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Medical School, 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Medical School, 1957-1960 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Medical School, 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Medical School, 1956-1957 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Medical School - General, 1957-1958 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Medical School, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Medical School, 1960-1961 (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Medical School, 1961-1962 (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Medical School, 1962-1963 (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Medical School, 1962-1963 (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Medical School, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Medical School - Administration, 1958-1959 (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Medical School - Administration, 1959-1960 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Medical School - Alumni Appeal, 1951-1952 (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Medical School - Architects and Brochures, 1953-1954 (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Medical School - Anatomy, 1944-1955 (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Medical School - Anatomy, 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Medical School - Anatomy, Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Medical School - Associate Dean, Associate General Secretary, 1957-1959 (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Medical School - Bacteriology, 1944-1955 (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Medical School - Medical Microbiology (Bacteriology), 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Medical School - Bacteriology and Experimental Pathology (Budget), 1955-1956 (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Medical School - Biochemistry, 1956-1957 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Medical School - Material for Brochure, 1952-1954 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Medical School - Buildings Maintenance and Alterations, 1950 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Medical School - By-Laws of Hospitals, Trustee's Committee on, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Medical School - Clippings, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Medical School - Faculty Committee: Curriculum Study, 1954 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Committee for Disposition of the Medical School (also called Clinical Committee, also called Special Committee on the Use of Stanford Medical School Facilities in San Francisco), 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Medical School - Commonwealth Fund, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Medical School - Dean Selection, 1952-1953 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Medical School - Dean Selection, 1952-1953 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Medical School - Dean Selection, 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Medical School - Dean Selection, 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Medical School - Dean's Letter, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Medical School - Federal Aid, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Medical School, 1956-1957 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Medical School - Dept. of Medicine (Budget), 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Medical School - Stanford Hosptial, 1950-1951 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Medical School - Stanford and Lane Hospitals, 1949-1950 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Medical School - Lane Hospital and Stanford Clinics deficit, 1951-1957 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Medical School - Lane and Stanford Hospitals, 1954-1955 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Medical School - Lane and Stanford Hospitals, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Medical School - Lane and Stanford Hospitals, 1956-1957 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Medical School - Lane and Stanford Hospitals, 1957-1958 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Medical School - Labor Medical Care, 1950-1952 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Medical School - Letters from Stanford Doctors, 1946-1953 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Medical School - Material on moving to campus, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Medical School - Masonic Memorial Hospital, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Medical School - Proposals to Commonwealth Fund, Masonic Hospital, etc., 1953 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Medical Center, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Medical Center Campaign (see also Medical Center Fund), 1953-1956 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Medical Center Fund, 1956-1957 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Medical School - Budget, 1956-1957 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Medical School - Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Medical School - Budget, 1954-1955 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Medical School - Misc. Cost Data, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Nursing, 1951 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Nursing, 1952 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Nursing, 1951-1952 (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Nursing, 1953 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Nursing, 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Nursing, 1953-1954 (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Nursing, 1954-1955 (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Nursing School, 1954-1955 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Nursing, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Nursing - Budget, 1955-1956 (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - Medical School - Obstetrics and Gynecology (Budget), 1954-1956 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Medical School - Pathology (Budget), 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Medical School - Pediatrics (Budget), 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Medical School - Pitch, 1955 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Medical School - Planning, 1954-1955 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Medical School - Pharmacology, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Medical School - Pharmacology, 1956-1957 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Medical School - Physical Therapy, 1951 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Medical School - Physical Therapy, 1951-1952 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Medical School - Physical Therapy, 1953 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Medical School - Physical Therapy, 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Medical School - Physical Therapy, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Medical School - Physical Therapy (Budget), 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Medical School - Physiology, 1949-1950 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Medical School - Physiology, 1950-1951 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  - Medical School - Physiology, 1952-1953 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Medical School - Physiology, 1953-1954 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Medical School - Physiology, 1954-1955 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Medical School - Physiology, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  - Medical School - Preventive Medicine (Budget), 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  - Medical School - Psychiatry, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  - Medical School - Radiology, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 22)
  - Medical School - Rehabilitation, 1955-1956 (Box 64, Folder 23)
  - Medical School - Report (Weeks, John Price Jones), 1951-1952 (Box 64, Folder 24)